MD ATIQULLAH KHAN

Full Stack Web Developer

■ mdatiqullahkhan2711@gmail.com 🕻 7903677126 🏶 https://ateeq2711.github.io/portfolio_1.1/

https://github.com/Ateeq2711 https://www.linkedin.com/in/mdatiqullahkhan2711/

Ambitious Java Developer having 1.4 year of experience in IT Industry comprising of Java enterprise web application development, maintenance & support.Excellent team player, Solution oriented professional having strong knowledge of Core Java, JDBC, JSF, Spring Boot, MySql, JSP, Hibernate, JavaScript.

Experience

HAMSA SOHAM HEALTHCARE PVT. LTD.

TRAINEE SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Patna,Bihar MAR 2023-NOV 2023

- Involved in developing web application (Loan Management System) for a well recognized government bank that helps automate every stage of the loan cycle, from new customer to loan closing that reduced the paper worked by 100%
- Developed facility to do survey of village, facility to store information of new customer, different types of loans provided by the bank.
- Developed facility to issue loan and keep record of all loans and a 5 level verification process.
- Developed facility to repayment where the month-wise loan collection should be done.
- Developed many useful reports.
- Technologies Used Java, JSF, JDBC, MSSQL, XHTML, PRIMEFACES, CSS

PSA INFOTECH.

BANGLORE JUN 2022-DEC 2022

FULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER INTERN

- CRM is a technology for managing all your company's relationships and interactions with customers and potential customers. The goal is to Improve business relationships. CRM system helps companies stay connected to customers, streamline processes, and improve profitability.
- Modules Login, Add Leads, Edit, Delete, Show Leads, Convert to contact, Compose mail, Billing
- Technologies Used Java, Springboot, Hibernate/JPA, MySql, JSP
- Tools Used Spring Tool Suite, MySql Workbench

Education

• B.TECH AKU 2017-2021

LOKNAYAK JAI PRAKASH INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

• PCT: 71.93 %

▲ 12Th CBSE-2016

· Doon Senior Secondary School

• PCT: 77.4 %

10Th CBSE-2014

- ST. JOSEPH SENIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL
- PCT: 89%

Skills

- Java
- SPRINGBOOT
- JDBC
- SERVLET
- HIBERNATE/JPA

- JSP
- JSF
- PRIMEFACES
- HTML
- CSS

- MYSQL
- MSSQL
- JavaScript
- RESTFUL API